絶|<ぜっ対|<た#|い零|<れ#|い度|<どへ
Taking me below the limit
Cold enough to freeze my spirit
薄|<う#|すれていく 感|<か#|ん情|<じょ#|うの余|<よ韻|<い#|ん
Till we fade away, transparent
Please don’t make this world coherent
息|<い#|きが途|<と切|<ぎれないように
歩|<あ#|るき出|<だした
（凍|<こ#|おった水|<す#|い平|<へ#|い線|<せ#|んに）(It feels so Cryogenic)
温|<お#|ん度|<どの無|<ない 突|<つき刺|<さすような風|<か#|ぜ
見|<みえなくなってしまった 微|<か#|すかな思|<お#|もい出|<で
「寂|<さ#|びしい」を押|<おし殺|<こ#|ろした 微|<び熱|<ね#|つで
(So wake me up, so wake me up from this silent maze)
I’ll watch as entropy runs out, far into the future
Or maybe tomorrow, without any overture
We’re left to sleep forever in this enclosure
(So wake me up, so wake me up from this silent maze)
熱|<ね#|つ的|<て#|き死|<しの軌|<き道|<ど#|う 何|<ど処|<こかにあるはずの分|<ぶ#|ん岐|<きを
We’re searching for what we’ve lost once more
探|<さ#|がしてるの
絶|<ぜっ対|<た#|い零|<れ#|い度|<どへ
I’ll sing out my final hopes
Resounding through these broken domes
囚|<と#|らわれてる 必|<ひ#|つ然|<ぜ#|んの重|<じゅ#|う力|<りょ#|く
Paralyzed, it won’t set us free
Silent noise is all we can see
消|<きえかけの希|<き望|<ぼ#|う 辿|<た#|どって
歩|<あ#|るき出|<だした
「It feels so Cryogenic」
Float into the void, where it all disappears
Banish all my thoughts, no more worries or fears
私|<わ#|た#|し 透|<と#|う明|<め#|いなんだ 氷|<こ#|お#|りのように
絶|<ぜっ対|<た#|い零|<れ#|い度|<どへ
Everything I know is fading,
In this snow, there’s no returning
余|<よ熱|<ね#|つが叫|<さ#|けんで 泣|<なくこの鼓|<こ動|<ど#|う
In a light that's so synthetic
[I] think my heart is Cryogenic
誰|<だ#|れかといないと 凍|<こ#|ごえそうで
歩|<あ#|るき出|<だした
I feel like I’ve wandered alone for so long
Yet still, I believe I’ll find warmth by the dawn
明日|<あ#|すに縋|<す#|がって目|<め指|<ざした アンタレスの星|<せ#|い図|<ず
法|<ほ#|う則|<そ#|くの零|<れ#|い点|<て#|ん 逆|<さ#|からって
歩|<あ#|るき出|<だした
（凍|<こ#|おった水|<す#|い平|<へ#|い線|<せ#|んに）(It feels so Cryogenic)